

MECHATRONIC ENGINEER

Details

6624763758 bgamezt@outlook.com

Links

Projects: brayangamez Portfolio

Skills	
jQuery	
Git	
HTML & CSS	
JavaScript	
Python	
Mongoose	
node	
Angular	
Django	
typescript	

Express.js

English

Spanish

French

Languages

Profile

I'm mechatronic engineer with a passion for coding. Currenly im open fullstack and front/backend opportunities. I've had expertise developing personal projects with different technologies such as JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.JS, MongoDB, JQuery, Express, but im willing to learn other kind of technologies and languajes. Here inside of this website you will be able to see some of my projects and the technologies which were used to coding it.

Employment History

manufacturing technician, Te connectivity, Hermosillo

FEBRUARY 2021 - PRESENT

- Repair machines related with crimping cables
- Make sure prevent maintenance in different machines
- Help with different set-ups in machines to work with
- · Look for different improvements in the area

Manufacturing engineer, Federal Electronics, Hermosillo

MAY 2019 - APRIL 2020

- Api in out products
- Timing
- · Corrective actions
- Interpretation of plans
- Support production lines

Employee, Ripasa CNC, Hermosillo

MAY 2018 - JULY 2018

- Measurement of tools
- milling and milling machine
- set-up machine
- Design and redesign of parts in CAD software

Education

bachelor's, Technology Institute of Hermosillo, Hermosillo

AUGUST 2013 - MARCH 2018